<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Layouts</string>
    <string name="name">Alex Ferguson</string>
    <string name="bio">Sir Alex Ferguson is the most successful manager in British football history, winning 13 Premier League titles with Manchester United.

Having spent all of his playing career in Scotland, Ferguson first went into management with East Stirlingshire in 1974 before joining St Mirren in the same year.

At St Mirren, Ferguson transformed a Second Division team into the 1977 First Division champions.

Ferguson further enhanced his reputation at Aberdeen, where he guided the club to three top-flight titles, four Scottish Cups, and triumphs in the UEFA Cup Winners\' Cup and UEFA Super Cup.

He replaced Ron Atkinson at Old Trafford in 1986, winning his first FA Cup in 1990. He also added another UEFA Cup Winners\' Cup and UEFA Super Cup to his collection.

Ferguson ended Man Utd’s 26-year wait for a top-flight title in the inaugural Premier League season of 1992/93. He went on to enjoy unprecedented success over the next two decades until his retirement at the end of the 2012/13 campaign.

The basis of the Red Devils\' success was the "Class of 92", with Ryan Giggs, David Beckham, Gary Neville, Phil Neville, Paul Scholes and Nicky Butt among the "Fergie’s fledglings" coming to prominence in the early to mid-1990s.

During his reign at Old Trafford, Ferguson also won the FA Cup five times and the League Cup on four occasions. United also claimed two UEFA Champions League trophies under his management, including the 1999 win in Barcelona with two stoppage-time goals in a 2-1 victory over Bayern Munich.

United’s 13th Premier League title and 20th top-flight triumph overall came with four matches to spare in 2012/13 as Ferguson exceeded 800 Premier League matches managed and 1,400 matches in all competitions.

In total, he lifted more than 30 trophies in his time in charge at Old Trafford.

He won Premier League Manager of the Season on 11 occasions, as well as picking up the monthly accolade 27 times and numerous other individual awards, such as LMA Manager of the Year and LMA Manager of the Decade.

His all-time Premier League record stands at 528 wins from 810 matches.</string>
    <string name="you_nickname">What is your nickname</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
</resources>